His Wife... His Mistress... His Career... A Deadly Trap
52 Pick-Up is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by John Frankenheimer.
Harry Mitchell is a successful Los Angeles manufacturer
whose wife is running for city council.
His life is turned upside down when three blackmailers confront him with a
videotape of him with his young mistress and demand $100,000.
Fearing that the story will hurt his wife's political campaign if he goes to the police,
Harry pretends that he will pay the men, but does not follow through.
Harry Mitchell, played by Roy Scheider.
Barbara Mitchell, played by Ann-Margret.
Doreen, played by Vanity.
Alan Raimy, played by John Glover.
Leo Franks, played by Robert Trebor.
Jim O'Boyle, played by Lonny Chapman.
52 Pick-Up is a 1986 American neo-noir crime film directed by John
Frankenheimer and starring Roy Scheider, Ann-Margret, and Vanity.
It is based on Elmore Leonard's 1974 novel 52 Pickup and is the
second adaptation of it after The Ambassador (1984).
The film explores themes of infidelity, based on novel
or book, blackmail, porn actor, murder.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.